In financial research, the hard part isn't writing the report.
It's making every line stand up to scrutiny.
TraceMind.
It turns investment research into an auditable chain — every thought, every tool call—
—every conclusion bound to a source.
You see the main thesis. You also see the alternative.
You see where the audit rules stop the model from overreaching.
Every citation is checked against the source it came from.
Risk is layered. The decision card delivers a clear rating, a confidence, and indicators to track.
The knowledge graph connects companies, customers, and regulators into one navigable network.
Follow-up questions build on prior evidence — no starting from scratch.
Research is no longer a black box. It's a path you can walk back. TraceMind. Every judgment, traceable.